Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student Records, 1998 -- 2018; UA235.001; 74.4 Linear Feet
  - Lee, Hyunkyung, 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Abdul-Korah, Morgan, 2017-08; UA235.001.093.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Ahern, Timothy S., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Asmar, Diane, 2017-06; UA235.001.093.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Asnaashari, Leila, 2017-06; UA235.001.093.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Assad, James R., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Bak, Anna G., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Baxley, Amelia S., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Berger, Eric J., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Bolis, Sarah L., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Bond, Charles T., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Bossie, Meagan M., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Boules, Mark M., 2017-08; UA235.001.093.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Boulos, Mina, 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - Braun, Gerald S., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Bressler, Brittany A., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Brigham, Diana L., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Brothers, Kara M., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Burison, Steven E., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - Cheung, Joseph, 2017-06; UA235.001.093.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - Chheda, Sonia H., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Choi, Kyu J., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 39)
  - Cornick, Gabriel H., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - Coutts, Leah S., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 41)
  - Creech, Grace, 2017-06; UA235.001.093.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 42)
  - Dalavurak, Katerina, 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 43)
  - Daneshgar, Philip, 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 44)
  - Daniel, Francis J., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 45)
  - De La Cruz, Ignacio I., 2017-08; UA235.001.093.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 46)
  - DeLorenzo, Aimee E., 2017-05; UA235.001.093.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 93, Folder 47)
  - Denike, Jennifer E., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Destenaves, Geoffroy, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Donohue, Jacob A., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Drubi, Martin, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Dubin, Max I., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Eckert, Pasquale P., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Fantone, Crista L., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Ferreiro, Claudia, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Fontaine, Alyssa L., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Ford, Christopher H., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Franklin, Farien C., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Galstian, Sona G., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Gendi, Monica R., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Gil, Sara, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Giordano, Elisa E., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Golkari, Sara, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Grandberry, Krystle, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - Guerrero, Vanessa A., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Halkias, Irene M., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Hamze, Houda W., 2013-08 -- 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Hardenbergh, William Evan, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Harper, Vance, 2017-06; UA235.001.094.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Htazipetrou, Kristina P., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - He, Ben-Li, 2017-06; UA235.001.094.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Hodges, Parker W., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Hoye, Patrick, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Hur, Byung, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - Huynh, David, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Innabi, Sandra, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Irby, Alexis, 2017-06; UA235.001.094.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - Jailwala, Mansi, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Kabbani, Nadia, 2017-06; UA235.001.094.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - Kaceli, Monika, 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - Arrigo, Michael P., 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - Case, James E., 2016-05 -- 2017-05; UA235.001.094.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Ausenda, Federico, 2016-05; UA235.001.094.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - Aziz, Fatima, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 37)
  - Bagher, Sara, 2016-05; UA235.001.094.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 38)
  - Barry, Reza, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 39)
  - Bello, Nicholas, 2016-08; UA235.001.094.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 40)
  - Belussi, Mirian E., 2016-07; UA235.001.094.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 41)
  - Buckley, Audra, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 42)
  - Carnow, Zachary, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 43)
  - Carpentino-DeJesus, Yissell, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 44)
  - Chan, Alice, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 45)
  - Chao, Min, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 46)
  - Choi, Hanel, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 47)
  - Chon, Anne, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 48)
  - Decoteau, Corey, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 49)
  - DellaRipa, Susan, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 50)
  - Gandhi, Sanyukta, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 51)
  - Ghandourah, Ezdehar, 2016-12; UA235.001.094.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 52)
  - Ghattas, Mary Hanna, 2016-06; UA235.001.094.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 53)
  - Homsi, Moetaz, 2016-06 -- 2016-07; UA235.001.094.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 94, Folder 54)
  - Angra, Saloni, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Aref, Heshem, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Bains, Amardeep, 2016-04; UA235.001.095.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Dani, Kunal V., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - De Leon, Risha, 2016-04; UA235.001.095.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Dhillon, Supreet K., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Juneja, Neha, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Kour, Manmeet, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Ouabira, Eman, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Patel, Bhavya J., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Singh, Prabhdeep, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Singh, Satwinder, 2016-04; UA235.001.095.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Thankachen, Deepti A., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Xu, Chendi, 2016-06; UA235.001.095.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Patel, Monica D., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Patel, Neil M., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Patel, Shivam A., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Pausma, Thomas D., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Penn, Christina, 2016-06; UA235.001.095.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Pesut, Christopher D., 2016-06; UA235.001.095.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Pham, Charles M., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Pham, Ngoc K., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Piacquadio, Christina, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Pineda Youniss, Camila X., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Pouzol, Stephanie, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Raptis, Olga, 2016-06; UA235.001.095.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Reisig, Jessie E., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Richer, Justin P., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Ritchie, Mark A., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Robinson, Rebecca J., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Courtney E., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Safer, Jason M., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Saffari, Shawheen S., 2016-06; UA235.001.095.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Saggar, Neha, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Sahni, Meera, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Samaha, Sara J., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Sanchez, Jairo A., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - Shah, Anjalee N., 2016-06; UA235.001.095.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 38)
  - Shamirian, Paul R., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 39)
  - Shim, Laura J., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 40)
  - Silard, Chrstopher E., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 41)
  - Small, Jesse, 2015-05 -- 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 42)
  - Smith, Kyle, 2016-07; UA235.001.095.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 43)
  - Soldin-Wassfi, Mariam C., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 44)
  - Steele, Jennifer L., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 45)
  - Su, Yuehang, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 46)
  - Sundaralingam, Shankeertha, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 47)
  - Tano, Anne Marie, 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 48)
  - Tay, Ronney Y., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 49)
  - Thayer, Halston W., 2016-05; UA235.001.095.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 95, Folder 50)
  - Tiruvadi, Avanthi S., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Treff, Sarah A., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Tsiao, Ashley, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Tsui, Tiffany A., 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Nguyen, Kevin, 2016-07; UA235.001.096.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Nguyen, Minh, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Nguyen, Sabrina, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Nimsuwan, Alissara G., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Nyakundi, Victor M., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Onyekaba, Michael, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Ormaza, Efren D., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Pak, Jin Woo, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Paolino, Christopher R., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Park, James, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Park, Ka E., 2016-07; UA235.001.096.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Patel, Amee J., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Patel, Felisha, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Patel, Khusbu P., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Patel, Khushbu G., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Patel, Krupa, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Phan, Anthony Minhduc H., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Welker, Ryan F., 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Williams, Tahira R., 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, Jennifer E., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Woldeselasie, Hiyab, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Wong, Jason, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Wood, Brittany M, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Wych, Steven, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Yoo, Christopher, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Zamora, Kristopher L., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Zang, Kathryn E., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Zeng, Xin, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Choi, Michael T., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Clancy, Myles R., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - Cohen, Rachel L., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Comstock, Stephen P., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Constantine, John M., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 37)
  - Cox, McKenna A., 2012-08 -- 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Crutcher, Vladik V., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - Daniels, Zachary, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 40)
  - Davis, Erica L., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 41)
  - Del Giorno, Raphael A., 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 42)
  - Demers, Sara M., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 43)
  - Devine, Matthew T., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 44)
  - Dinh, Kim, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 45)
  - Dooley, Daniel M., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 46)
  - Draper, Camille M., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 47)
  - Dunkling, Angela, 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 48)
  - Dykes, Marissa, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 49)
  - Farah, Jacqueline, 2016-06; UA235.001.096.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 50)
  - Fixelle, Noah D., 2016-05; UA235.001.096.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 96, Folder 51)
  - Fowler, Charlotte A., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Franklin, Robert L., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Fung, Katharina S., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Garber, Yamila, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Garnache, Michelle M., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Gera, Yogesh, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Gilman, Hannah E., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Guarino, Matthew A., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Guerra, Francis, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Gurrant, Elizabeth A., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Hackbarth, Mallory J., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Hall, Joshua J., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Hanna, Monica M., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Harlan, Mia H., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Hauer, Johanna M., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Hayek, Gabriel M., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Hedstrom, Brien, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Heo, Yoon-Young, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Hsin, Ronald, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Huckel, Kiersten F., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Irani, Ali, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Kang, Paul K., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Kapotes, Zachary, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Keck, Samantha L., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Kelly, Caitlin M., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Khetarpal, Sheena, 2016-07; UA235.001.097.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Kim, Amy M., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Kim, Douglas W., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Kim, Julia J., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Kim, Jung Yeon, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Kim, Paul, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - Kim, Soung, 2016-08; UA235.001.097.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - Kim, Yun A., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - Kunkel, Heidi J., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - Kwon, Junsoo, 2016-07; UA235.001.097.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - Larrabee, Eben, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - Lau, Vicente, 2016-07; UA235.001.097.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - Leikin, Jennie D., 2015-05 -- 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - Leung, Heather, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Li, Diana, 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - Li, Yu, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 41)
  - MacIntyre, Christen M., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 42)
  - Mahdavi, Maryam, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 43)
  - Manzi, Matthew J., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 44)
  - Mariano, Alissa B., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 45)
  - Marshall, Michael A., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 46)
  - Martirosyan, Samuel, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 47)
  - Marzouca, Lauren E., 2016-04; UA235.001.097.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 48)
  - Mateo, Alfredo G., 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 49)
  - Mattison, Bradford R., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 50)
  - Ng, Rebecca W., 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 51)
  - Nguyen, Dorothy K., 2016-07; UA235.001.097.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 52)
  - Natto, Zuhair, 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 53)
  - Natto, Zuhair, 2016-05; UA235.001.097.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 54)
  - Opaneye, Oluwakare, 2016-06; UA235.001.097.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 97, Folder 55)
  - Lee, Michelle, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Frost, Gregory D., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - El-Youssef, Leila, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Cardona, Catalina, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Castellucci, Chiara L., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Castera, Anne Christine S., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Cekalniku, Lirie, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Chao, William, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Chen, Jimmy, 2016-04; UA235.001.098.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Chen, Jingjing, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Chen, Nan, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Ahmadian, Sheeva, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Alamwala, MaNDEEP Mandy K., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Albright, Amelia, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Annese, Alexander A., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Archer, Vincent W, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Arditi, Sibel, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Asha, Kourosh, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Aziz, Saadia A., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Baldwin, Riley J., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Barra, Mohammad, 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Barton, Jennifer L., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Beaulieu, Brett S., 2016-07; UA235.001.098.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Belous, Bradley T., 2016-04; UA235.001.098.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Beninati, Christopher J., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - Bishop, Jonathan, 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - Boschetti, Michael M., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Brady, Tyler K., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - Bries, Britney, 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - Borwn, Michael W., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - Brown, Nusi P., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Brown, William P., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - Cabral, Michael J., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - Canesi, Ryan A., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - Bonnell, Leah K., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - Ahluwalia, Ivy P., 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 36)
  - Aladmawy, Majdi A., 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 37)
  - Aladmawy, Majdi A., 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 38)
  - Alharthi, Shatha S., 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 39)
  - Alharthi, Shatha S., 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 40)
  - Alkandari, Naser, 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 41)
  - Almotlag, Sarah K., 2016-09; UA235.001.098.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 42)
  - Alsahfi, Rashed, 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 43)